Register of the Marvin Liebman Papers, 1953-1992
Hoover Institution Archives
Marvin Liebman Papers,
1953-1992
69013
Liebman, Marvin
150 manuscript boxes, 4 oversize boxes, 1 album box, 7 envelopes, 5 phonotape reels. (65 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Correspondence, printed matter, press releases, campaign literature, reports, and photographs, relating to activities of American conservative and anti-communist organizations, including many involved with Asian and African affairs. Includes records of the firm Marvin Liebman Associates.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Access Points
Committee of One Million.; Anti-communist movements--United States.; Communism.; Communism--Africa.; Communism--Asia.; Africa.; Asia.; United States--Politics and government.; United States--Foreign relations.; United States--Foreign relations--1945-1989.; United States--Politics and government--1945-1989.; Conservatism.; Phonotapes.; Marvin Liebman Associates.
Historical Note
Marvin Liebman Associates, Inc., founded in 1958 by Marvin Liebman, was a New York Public relations firm engaged in lobbying for conservative and/or anti-communist organizations in the United States and abroad. Its services for clients included promoting public meetings, organizing sponsoring committees of distinguished citizens, compiling mailing lists, administering mail campaigns, publishing press releases, and effecting publicity. Its offices also served as headquarters for some organizations. The firm discontinued operations in 1969.
Clients of particular importance were the American African Affairs Association, American Afro-Asian Educational Exchange, American Committee for Aid to Katanga Freedom Fighters, American Conservative Union, American Emergency Committee on the Panama Canal, Assembly of Captive European Nations, William F. Buckley, Jr. for Mayor, Committee for the Monroe Doctrine, Committee of one million, Draft Goldwater Movement, National Committee Against the Treaty of Moscow, National Committee for Justice for Dodd, Tshombe Emergency Committee, World Congress for Freedom, and Young Americans for Freedom.
Series Description
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1953-1969. (Boxes 1-37)
  Arranged alphabetically by correspondent
- SUBJECT FILE, 1953-1969. (Boxes 38-108)
  Memoranda, reports, minutes of meetings, notes, endorsements, cards, press releases, campaign material, financial records, printed and other matter, arranged alphabetically by title or subject
- Increments (Boxes 109-153)
  (received in 1981 and 1993)
Container List
- Correspondence, 1953-1969
  - American African Affairs Association, 1965-1968 (Box 1-4.)
  - American Afro-Asian Educational Exchange, Inc., 1962-1968 (Box 5-6.)
  - American Afro-Asian Educational Exchange, Inc., 1962-1968 (Box 7.)
  - American Conservative Academy, 1962
  - American Conservative Union, 1962-1967
  - American Constitutional Action, 1965
  - American Economic Foundation, 1964-1968
  - American Emergency Committee on the Panama Canal, 1967-1968 (Box 8.)
  - American Friends of Vietnam, 1967
  - American Jewish League Against Communism, Inc., 1961-1963
  - American-Philippine Science Foundation, 1958-1959
  - American Public Affairs Educational Fund, Inc., 1965
  - Ash, Beatrice, 1963-1964
  - Asian Peoples anti-Communist League, 1959, 1965-1966
  - Assembly of Captive European Nations, 1960-1962
  - Blaine Amendment, 1967
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1964
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1964 (Box 9.)
  - Bundy, Edgar C., 1964-1969
  - Christian anti-Communist Crusade, 1962-1963
  - Clergymen's Emergency Committee on China, 1966-1968
  - Committee for Freedom for all Peoples, 1960
  - Committee for Religious Liberty, 1963
  - Committee for the Monroe Doctrine, 1962-1964
  - Committee for the Monroe Doctrine, 1962-1964 (Box 10.)
  - Committee for the Monroe Doctrine, 1962-1964 (Box 11.)
  - Committee of one million
    - Alsop, Joseph H., 1963
    - Ashbrook, John M., 1966
    - Asian People anti-Communist League, 1959, 1965-1966
    - Assembly of Captive European Nations, 1960-1962
    - Austin, Warren R., 1962
    - Bouscaren, Anthony, 1966 (Box 12.)
    - Buchanon, John Jr., 1967
    - Businessmen's Committee on Trade with Red China, 1966-1968
    - Businessmen's Committee on Trade with Red China, 1966-1968 (Box 13.)
    - Christian Anti-Communist Crusade, 1962-1963 (Box 14.)
    - Clark, Harrison, 1965 (Box 15.)
    - Committee for End Aid to the Soviet Enemy (CEASE), 1966-1968
    - Committee of one million 1964 Olympics Game
    - Committee of one million, miscellany, 1959-1968
    - Committee of one million, miscellany, 1959-1968 (Box 16-19.)
    - Committee of one million Miscellany (Box 20.)
    - Cronin, Walter F., 1961
    - Davis, Clifford, 1962
    - Day, Henry L., 1961
    - Deininger, James V., 1962
    - Deininger, W. T., 1962
    - Democratic National Convention Platforms Committee
    - Dens, A. J., 1962
    - Dillman, H. A., 1962
    - Dobriansky, Lev E., 1961
    - Dodd, Thomas J., 1964-1968
    - Dominick, Peter H., 1964-1968
    - Dorn, William Jennings Bryan, 1961
    - Dos Passos, John, 1964
    - Douglas, Paul, 1960-1966 (Box 21.)
    - Douglas, William O., 1961
    - Doyle, Clyde, 1961
    - Drew, Austin R., 1962
    - Dubil, W. J., 1962
    - Dull, Margaret, 1962
    - Eastland, James O., 1961
    - Edison, Charles, 1960-1962
    - Edwards, Lee, 1966-1968
    - Ellsworth, Robert E., 1961
    - Emmet, Christopher, 1963
    - Erasik, Louis, 1961
    - Evans, W. H., Jr., 1961
    - Field, R. Harrison, 1962
    - Fisher, John M., 1962
    - Fitzsimmons, Vernon, 1961
    - Foley, Anne D., (Mrs.), 1961
    - Forrestal, Laurence, 1961
    - Fournier, Laurence J., 1961
    - Fox, Charles, 1961
    - Frick, Helen C., 1961
    - Fritz, Edward C., 1961
    - Fulcher, Thomas, K., 1961
    - Garside, B. A., Dr., 1961-1967
    - Gibbon, C. F., n.d.
    - The Indianapolis News, n.d.
    - Javits, Jacob K., 1965-1966
    - Judd, Walter H., 1966-1967 (Box 22.)
    - Keating, Kenneth B., 1961
    - King, Harold, 1960
    - Labin, Suzanne, n.d.
    - League of Women Voters, 1966-1967
    - Liberalism Towards Red China, 1966 (Box 23.)
    - Liebman, Marvin, 1953-1969
    - Lin, Fu-shun, 1966
    - Lindsay, Albert J., 1960
    - MacCallum, E. J., Jr., 1961
    - Mandel, Ben, n.d.
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1961-1962
    - New York Times, 1963-1968
    - Red China lobby, 1960-1961
    - Rickenbacker, Eddie, 1960 (Box 24.)
    - Roper Research Associates and Gallup Organization, Inc. 1967
    - Shu-Kai, Chow, 1967
    - Smith, Alexander, 1961-1967
    - Sockman, Ralph W., 1958
    - Steering Committee, 1961-1968
    - Student Committee for a Free China, 1963-1968
    - Tung, Shin-Tsin, 1964
    - United States Departments of State and Treasury, 1960
    - Van Malsen, Bent, 1960
    - Weil, Carl E., 1960
    - Zabloske, Clement J., 1966
  - Committee on Pan American Policy, 1965 (Box 25.)
  - Communications Distribution, 1961-1965
  - Communications Distribution, 1961-1965 (Box 26.)
  - Communications Distribution, 1961-1965 (Box 27.)
  - Council for an American Foreign Policy, 1963-1964
  - Council on Communist Anti-Semitic Policy and Practices, 1967-1968
  - Eaton, Cyrus, 1960 (Box 28.)
  - Edison, Charles, 1962-1963
  - Edwards, Lee and Associates, 1968
  - El A(o Espa(ol, 1964
  - Emergency Committee for Chinese, 1962-1963
  - Fitch, Geraldine, 1958-1961 (Box 29.)
  - Free Asia Association, 1961
  - Friends of Rhodesian Independence, 1966-1967
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1964
  - Group Research, Inc., 1967
  - Historical Research Foundation, 1962
  - International Research on Communist Techniques, Inc., 1958
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1959-1962
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1959-1962 (Box 30.)
  - Kultura Group (anti-Communist exiles), 1968
  - Lasky, (Victor) Project, 1963
  - Miscellany
  - Miscellany (Box 31.)
  - National Committee Against the Treaty of Moscow, 1963
  - National Committee Against the Treaty of Moscow, 1963 (Box 32.)
  - National Committee for Justice for Dodd, 1967 (Box 33.)
  - National Committee for the Reelection of Walter H. Judd, 1960-1963
  - National Schools Committee for Economic Education, 1967
  - Next of Kin Statement (Viet Nam), 1964
  - New York Republican Education and Action Program, 1964-1965
  - People's Emergency Committee Against Communist Aggression, 1965 (Box 34.)
  - Portugal's Public Relations in the U.S., 1964-1965
  - Tshombe (Moise) Emergency Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 35.)
  - United States Press Association, 1962-1964
  - Vigurie, Richard A., 1968
  - World Youth Crusade for Freedom, 1966-1967
  - World Youth Crusade for Freedom, 1966-1967 (Box 36.)
  - World Youth Crusade for Freedom, 1966-1967 (Box 37.)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1964-1968
- Subject File, 1953-1969
  - American African Affairs, 1965-1968 (Box 38-42.)
  - American African Affairs, 1965-1968 (Box 43.)
  - American Afro-Asian Educational Exchange, Inc., 1962-1968
  - American Afro-Asian Educational Exchange, Inc., 1962-1968 (Box 44-50.)
  - American-Asian Educational Exchange, 1960-1969 (Box 51-55.)
  - American-Asian Educational Exchange, 1960-1969 (Box 56.)
  - American Committee for Aid to Katanga Freedom Fighters, 1961-1963
  - American Committee for Aid to Katanga Freedom Fighters, 1961-1963 (Box 57.)
  - American Conservative Union, 1962-1966
  - American Conservative Union, 1962-1966 (Box 58.)
  - American Conservative Union, 1962-1966 (Box 59.)
  - Americans for Conservative Action, 1961
  - American Council for Responsible Free Trade Policies, 1962
  - American Emergency Committee for Tibetan Refugees, 1964-1967
  - American Emergency Committee on the Panama Canal, 1967-1968 (Box 60-61.)
  - American Jewish Association, 1968 (Box 62.)
  - American Security Council, 1963-1968
  - Association for Asian Studies, 1968
  - Blaine Amendment, 1967
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1965-1968
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1965-1968 (Box 63.)
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1965-1968 (Box 64.)
  - Clergymen's Emergency Committee on China, 1966-1968
  - Committee for the Monroe Doctrine, 1962-1964 (Box 65-66.)
  - Committee for the Monroe Doctrine, 1962-1964 (Box 67.)
  - Committee of One Million
    - Advertisement for Committee, 1966
    - Appeasement--Ally of Red China, 1966
    - "Appeasement to Red China," a script of C.O.M. film, 1965 Audit, 1966
    - Businessmen's Committee on Trade with Red China, 1966-1968 (Box 68.)
    - Candidate's Kit, 1966-1968
    - Chronological listing, April 6, 1960 - April 11, 1961 (Box 69-76.)
    - Citizen Committee for Peace with Freedom in Vietnam, 1967 (Box 77.)
    - Clergyman's poll, 1958
    - Committee of One Million and Committee on Foreign Relations, 1963
    - Committee of One Million against the Admission of Communist China to the United Nations, history, 1965
    - Committee for Freedom for All Peoples, 1960
    - Committee for a Review of our China Policy, 1963
    - Congressional acceptances, 1964
    - Congressional declaration, 1962
    - Congressional endorsers, 1964-1968
    - Congressional endorsements to Committee for Million's 1963 Statement, 1964-1968
    - Congressional signers removed from Committee of One Million's list, 1966
    - Conventions, 1964-1968
    - Council against Communist Aggression 1966-1968 (Box 78.)
    - Dominick, Peter H., "Red China and the United Nations," 1961-1966, an unpublished typewritten article.
    - Election, mailing, 1964
    - Endorsers opposed to trade with Red China, n.d.
    - Endorsers to 1955 acceptance cards (Box 79.)
    - Endorsers, 1962
    - Folksongs for Conservatives, 1963. A published article by Noel Parmentel, Jr.
    - Fund-raising letter, 1965 (Box 80.)
    - Free Pacific Association, 1965-1966
    - Friends for a Free China, 1960-1963
    - Gibbon, C. F., "When the Kissing had Stopped," n.d. An unpublished typewritten article
    - Grew, Joseph, 1965
    - Hornbeck, Stanley K., 1964
    - Judd, Walter, "Keep Red China Out," 1967. An unpublished article
    - Kubek, A., China material, 1963
    - Liebman, Marvin, memoranda regarding Committee of One Million
      - Memoranda regarding Committee of One Million on 1961
      - "DeGaulle and Red China," n.d.
    - Martin, David, "Shall We Change Our Policy?" 1968. An unpublished typescript (Box 81.)
    - Memoranda, 1954-1958
    - Mid-Atlantic and New England Conference on China and the U.S., April 21-23, 1967
    - National Committee on United States-China Relations, 1966-1969
    - Newsletters, 1958
    - Newspaper articles on China and Foreign policy, 1966-1968 (Box 82.)
    - Nielson Associates Inc., "Red China and its unacceptability for a seat in the U.N.," n.d. An unpublished draft
    - 1962 "Declaration" on Communist China
    - 1963 "Declaration" on Communist China
    - Non-endorsers to 1964 Statement
    - Old Files, 1957
    - "Red China and the American Negro," 1968, printed copy
    - Petition campaign, 1961-1965
    - Petition campaign, 1961-1965 (Box 83.)
    - Press Releases, 1964-1965
    - Program mailings, 1964
    - Radford, Arthur, "U.S. Policy Toward Red China," n.d.
      - An unpublished typewritten article
    - "The Recognitionists and Admiral A. Radford," 1963
      - An unpublished article
    - "Red China Outlaw" (a film), 1961
    - "Red China Speaks," a printed copy of an unpublished article, 1965
    - Report of the Committee to Explore Trade Possibilities with the People's Republic of China, 1964
    - Reorganization of the Steering Committee, 1964
    - Republican Platforms, 1956, 1960, and 1964
    - Sample mailings for Congressional endeavors, 1965
    - Signatures-endorsers of Committee of One Million's statement of position of U.S. policy toward Communist China, n.d.
    - Statement in rebuttal of Roger Hilsman's speech, 1963 (Box 84.)
    - Statement on China, 1968
    - Statement on China for Nixon, 1968
    - Statement on Trade with Red China, 1963
    - Steering Committee minutes, 1961-1968
    - Tsing, T. F. (Ambassador to the U.N.), 1965
    - United Nations speeches for Committee of One Million pamphlet, 1968
    - United States policy toward Red China by various U.S. Senators, 1966-1968
    - "Who is Isolating Red China," a study by the Committee of One Million, 1968
  - Communications Distribution Inc., 1961-1965 (Box 85.)
  - Conscience of a Conservative (an outline for a film), 1962
  - Conservative Party of New York State, 1961-1968
  - Council for an American Foreign Policy, 1963-1964
  - Council on Communist Anti-Semitic Policy and Practice, 1967-1968 (Box 86.)
  - Douglas, Paul H., statement, 1966
  - Edison, (Charles) Dinner Committee, 1963
  - Edison, (Charles) Dinner Committee (Box 87.)
  - Emergency Committee for Chinese Refugee members, 1964-1967 (Box 88.)
  - Finances of the Right Wing, 1964. Special Report #16
  - 52 Association Inc., 1966
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1964
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1964 (Box 89-92.)
  - Hamilton Wright Organization, Inc., 1958-1959 (Box 93.)
  - Jewish Council Against Communism, 1963
  - Judd, Walter H., 1960
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1959-1962 (Box 94.)
  - Leiss, Amelia C., ed., "Apartheid and United Nations, Collective Measures." A pamphlet prepared under the auspices of the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace.
  - McGraw-Edison Co., 1959-1963
  - McGraw-Edison Co., 1959-1963 (Box 95-96.)
  - Miscellany, 1966-1968 (Box 97.)
  - National Committee Against the Treaty of Moscow, 1963
  - National Committee for Justice for Dodd (Senator Thomas J. Dodd, D-Conn.), 1967 (Box 98.)
  - National Family Councilor Drug Addiction, n.d.
  - National Review, 1961-1966 (Box 99-100.)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1959 (Box 101.)
  - New York Committee on Public Safety, 1966
  - New York Republican Education and Cation Program, 1964-1965
  - New York State Republican Associations, 1964-1965
  - Next of Kin statement (Viet Nam), 1964
  - Overseas Press Club, 1962 (Box 102.)
  - Pamphlets on miscellaneous world communism and anti-American activities, 1958-1968
  - People's Emergency Committee, 1965
  - Polling operations, 1958 (Box 103.)
  - Promotion, 1968
  - Republicans for Buckley (James L. Buckley for Senator), 1968
  - Republicans for Buckley (James L. Buckley for Senator), 1968 (Box 104.)
  - Tshombe (Moise) Emergency Committee, 1967
  - Tshombe (Moise) Emergency Committee, 1967 (Box 105.)
  - Tshombe (Moise) Emergency Committee, 1967 (Box 106.)
  - "U.S. Soviet agreement to Neutralize Seattle, Washington, 1962." A published article by Margaret Greenfield.
  - Van Den Haag, "The War in Katanga," 1962. A published report World Anti-Communist Congress, 1958
  - World Youth Crusade for Freedom, 1967 (Box 107.)
  - World Youth Crusade for Freedom, 1967 (Box 108.)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1964-1968
- Increment
  (received in 1981)
  - American-Chilean Council (Box 109.)
    - Correspondence
      - A
      - American Security Council
      - Amnesty International
      - Amunategui, J.
      - Articles of association
      - B
      - Bauman, Robert E.
      - Berenson, Mark
      - Black, Charles
      - Blaustein, Albert P.
      - Braden, Spruille
      - British-Chilean Council (Box 110.)
      - Buckley, William F., Jr.
      - Bunster, Max and Ignacio
      - Butler, Ed (Information Council of the Americas)
      - Burnham, James
      - C
      - Castellanos, Sylvia
      - Chachis, George
      - Chamberlain, John
      - Chamudes, Marcos
      - Columnists, Miscellaneous
      - Columnists, Mailgram to, Jan. 9, 1979 (Box 111.)
      - Contributions and potential contributors
      - Consejo Chileno Norteamericano
      - Correspondence, Miscellaneous
      - Counterspy
      - D
      - De Toledano, Ralph
      - Devine, C. Robert
      - Dunn, Paxton
      - E
      - Edwards, Lee, and Associates, and Lynn
      - Francis Bouchey
      - Experience, Inc.
      - F
      - Finkelstein, Arthur J., and Gallup poll
      - Fetterman, Dan G. (The Rising Tide; Freedom Leadership Foundation)
      - Foreign companies and foreign addresses
      - Freedom Studies Center of the Institute for American Strategy (John M. Fisher)
      - "Frei Unleashes Public Criticism on His Own Government" (Translation)
      - Freivalds, John (Experience, Inc.)
      - Fundraising
      - G (Box 112.)
      - H
      - Hart, Jeffrey
      - Heritage Foundation
      - Holden, David
      - Holzer, Philip
      - Hopping, Bruce S. (Kalos Kagathos Foundation)
      - Human Events
      - I
      - Ibanez, Pedro
      - Inter-American Conference (American Council for World Freedom)
      - Interspec, Inc.
      - Intercollegiate Studies Institute (James B. Taylor) (Box 113.)
      - J
      - Journalist trips, Apr. 1976
      - Jacobs, Walter Darnell
      - Jordan, David C. (University of Virginia)
      - Judd, Walter H.
      - Korry, Edward
      - K
      - L
      - Kilpatrick, James Jackson
      - Kirk, Grayson
      - Lasky, Victor
      - Lefever, Ernest W.
      - Lists
      - Lists - Newsletter requests - "The Right Report"
      - Livingston, Goodhue
      - Lofton, John, Jr.
      - Lodge, John Davis
      - London trip, June 1978
      - Lopez, Carlos (Menlo College)
      - Lobbying reports
      - Lopez, Carlos - Pamphlet (Box 114.)
      - Luce Press Clippings
      - Lynch, Kevin (National Review)
      - Lyons, Eugene
      - Members and potential members
      - M
      - Microfiche
      - McMillin, Dan S. (Greater Kansas City Foreign-Trade Zone)
      - Mindszenty, Cardinal, Foundation (Ad Sell Company)
      - Moss, Robert
      - N
      - National Strategy Information Center (Box 115.)
      - Newspaper clippings
      - O
      - O'Lessker, Karl - Trip to Chile
      - Orchard, Carlos A.
      - Organization of American States - Booklet
      - Ossa, Nena
      - P (Box 116.)
      - Padev, Michael
      - Pamphlets
      - Pearson, Ronald W.
      - P.E.N.
      - Phillips, Ruby Hart
      - Possony, Stefan T.
      - Postal Receipts, etc.
      - Private Practice (Llewellyn H. Rockwell, Jr.) (Box 117.)
        - PR Newswire
      - Prospective writers
      - Prospective trips to Chile
      - PSA mailing list
      - Purcell, Robert W.
      - R
      - Receptions
      - Replies to newspaper articles and editorials
      - Reports and memoranda
      - Richardson, Elliot L. - Trip to Chile
      - Rickenbacker, William F.
      - Rockwell, Llewellyn H., Jr. - Trip to Chile
      - Rowe, David N.
      - Rusher, William A. - Trip to Chile
      - Ryan, Patrick J., and Clayton R. Barrow, Jr.
      - S
      - Schneider, William
      - Senese, Donald J. - Trip to Chile
      - Steibel, Warren
      - Stone, Roger
      - Syndicated columns
      - T
      - Taylor, Carl Joe (Box 118.)
      - Theberge, James D.
      - Times of the Americas
      - Translations
      - Trips to Chile - Members
      - Trucco, Manuel
      - U
      - Ultra Arts - Chile
      - V
      - Varney, Harold Lord (Committee on Pan American Policy)
      - W
      - Waldheim, Kurt
      - Wallace, DeWitt
      - Whelan, James R.
      - World Youth Crusade for Freedom
      - Wells, Samuel I., Jr.
      - X-Y
      - Young Americans for Freedom
    - Mailings, 1975-1978
      - Report, Nov. 1978
      - Report, Oct. 1978
      - Report, Sept. 1978, and New Guard reprint
      - Report, July 1978, "Towards a New Order in Chile," and "A Chile Wind of Change"
      - Report, June 1978, and International Finance reprint
      - Report, May 1978, and John Davis Lodge letter
      - Report, March 1978, and William A. Rusher letter
      - Report, Feb. 1978, and "Chilean Spring?"
      - Report, Jan. 1978, and letter
      - John Davis Lodge fundraising letter, May 1979
      - Report, May 1979
      - Report, Mar. - Apr. 1979 (Box 119.)
      - John Davis Lodge fundraising letter, Feb. 1979
      - Washington Weekly, Mar. 1979
      - Report, Jan. - Feb. 1979
      - Memorandum to members re U.S. Department of Justice complaint, Dec. 1978
      - Report, Dec. 1978
      - Report, Dec. 1977
      - Report, Oct. 1977, and John Davis Lodge fundraising appeal
      - Memorandum to members and friends re charter trip to Chile, Oct. 1977
      - Report, Sept. 1977, Private Practice reprint, and Spruille Braden fundraising appeal
      - Report, Aug. 1977, and memorandum to members and friends re recent developments
      - Report, June 1977, and Firing Line transcript (Box 120.)
      - Report, Apr. 1977, and New York Times reprint
      - Report, May 1977, and fundraising letter
      - Letter to Chilean companies, Apr. 1977
      - Report, Mar. 1977, Spruille Braden speech, and overseas letter
      - Report, Feb. 1977, and memorandum
      - Report, Jan. 1977, memorandum, and Spruille Braden fundraising letter
      - Report, Nov. 1976, fundraising letter, and Michael Padev pamphlet
      - John Chamberlain columns, July 1976
      - Report, Sept. 1976
      - Report, June 1976, and "Soviet Penetration of Latin America"
      - Report, May 1976, and press release re Cuban demonstration
      - Spruille Braden letter, Apr. 1976, and Senate colloquium on Chile
      - Washington Report, Jan. 1976
      - Report, Feb. 1976
      - Larry P. McDonald reprint, and "Chile's Defense Needs," Feb. 1976 (Box 121.)
      - Report, Jan. 1976, and Robert E. Bauman fundraising appeal
      - Report, Dec. 1975
      - Robert Moss reprint, Oct. 1975
      - "Chile" (pamphlet), Aug. 1975
      - Victor Lasky pamphlet, Sept. 1975
      - "Chile and Peru" (pamphlet), July 1975